pps.org 2009-11-18

# Project for Public Spaces Refund Policy

## Privacy/Refund Policy

Project for Public Spaces is a nonprofit organization dedicated to helping people create and sustain public spaces that build stronger communities. 

### Choose a topic:

## Privacy

  * Our Commitment to Your Privacy
  * Reading or Downloading
  * User Profile and Donations
  * Sending us an Email
  * Opt-Out or Change Your Contact Information
  * Use of Links
  * Use of Text and Images
  * Questions about our policies

## Refunds

  * General Policy
  * Publications
  * Membership
  * Donations
  * Training
  * Technical Assistance

#### Our Commitment to Your Privacy

We have written this statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to, and respect for, your privacy. We do not collect personally identifying information about you when you visit our site unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing this information is strictly voluntary. This policy is your guide to how we will handle information we learn about you from your visit to our Web site.

Return to Top

#### Reading or Downloading

We collect and store only the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet (for example, aol.com, if you are connecting from an America Online account, or princeton.edu if you are connecting from Princeton University's domain), the date and time you access our site, and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked to our site. We use the information we collect to measure the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, and to help us make our site more useful.

Return to Top

#### User Profile and Donations

If you complete the User Profile update form and share your personally identifying information, this information will be used only to provide you with more targeted content. We may use your contact information to send further information about our organization, or to contact you if necessary. You may always opt-out of receiving e-mails; see the "Opt Out" section below. We do not sell or share our mailing list with other organizations.

Return to Top

#### Sending us an Email

You may send us personally identifying information, for example, in an electronic mail message containing a question or comment, or by filling out a Web form that provides us this information. We use personally identifying information from email primarily to respond to your requests. We may forward your email to other employees who are better able to answer you questions. We may also use your email to contact you in the future about our programs that may be of interest.

We want to be very clear: We will not obtain personally identifying information about you when you visit our site unless you choose to provide such information to us. Providing such information is strictly voluntary. Except as might be required by law, we do not share any information we receive with any outside parties. 

Return to Top

#### Opt-Out or Change Your Contact Information

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us through a special online form. You may choose to receive only specific communications or none at all. You may also update your contact information previously provided to us through another online form. You cannot remove yourself from our database, but you can prevent unwanted communication.

Return to Top

#### Use of Links

Throughout our Web site, we provide links to other sites which may contain information of interest to our readers. We take no responsibility for, and exercise no control over the views, or accuracy of the information contained on other sites.

Creating a text link from your Web site to ours DOES require permission. If you would like permission to link to us, or have a link you'd like us to consider adding to our Web site, please send an email to [info@pps.org](mailto:info@pps.org) with the subject "Link request."

Return to Top

#### Use of Text and Images

If you would like to publish information that you find on our Web site, please send your request to [info@pps.org](http://www.leukemia-research.org/info@pps.org). The text, logo(s), and images on our site are protected by copyright, and our written permission is required before you use them.

Return to Top

#### Questions about our policies

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us at [info@pps.org](mailto:info@pps.org).

Return to Top

#### General Policy

PPS is a non-profit organization. As such, refunds will generally not be provided. However, PPS may consider refunds on a case-by-case basis. To request a refund, contact PPS at (212) 620-5660.

Return to Top

#### Publications

PPS makes every effort to ensure that customers receive the product they have ordered. In cases where customers receive incorrect or damaged books, PPS will remedy the situation promptly and professionally. 

PPS is only under obligation to accept returns and refund in cases where customers receive a product:

  1. in damaged condition;
  2. that they didn’t order; or
  3. that is not what they were led to expect (e.g. the product does not match a description or sample they were given).

In these cases, PPS will refund the price in full and will reimburse the customer for any reasonable charges involved with the return of the product. If the customer prefers, we may provide credit or arrange a suitable exchange in place of a refund. 

ALL refunds are dependent on the return of the product to PPS in the same/similar packaging as it was delivered, and in saleable condition (except in cases where a damaged product was delivered). 

PPS will NOT send products to customers, on consignment (as sample items), to be purchased at their discretion. 

PPS will not refund, credit or exchange products if the customer has received the goods they ordered and simply changes his/her mind. PPS values our customers; however, as a non-profit organization, lacks the resources (staff and financial) to refund orders filled properly. 

If customers insist, they are invited to state the matter in writing and send it to:

> Marcos Martinez  
>  Project for Public Spaces  
>  700 Broadway, 4th Fl  
>  New York, NY 10003

In certain cases, PPS will accept returns from customers who, acting in good faith, have received a book that was ‘not what they were after.’ This decision is to be made at the discretion of the Operations Director and/or Finance Officer on condition that:

  1. PPS will NOT reimburse the customer for the delivery cost of returning the book;
  2. refund will only be given if the book is returned in the same/similar packaging and in saleable condition; and
  3. the refund will be paid less the postage and handling costs associated with the original order and less an administrative fee for processing the return of the goods.

PPS will NOT refund customers who simply return books without an adequate reason. If customers are ineligible for refund, we will inform them that they must incur the cost of resending the products. 

If customers are not satisfied with the returns/refunds process, they may contact: 

Phone: (212) 620- 5660  
Email: info@pps.org

Return to Top

#### Membership

PPS memberships are not transferable. Payments for PPS memberships are final and non-refundable.

Return to Top

#### Donations

Donations to PPS are final and non-refundable.

Return to Top

#### Training

Registrations for training courses are non-refundable including no-shows.

If you contact us the day before the event, you may transfer your registration to an alternate event.

If PPS cancels or reschedule an event, you will be given the option to transfer your registration to a new event time or to receive a full refund.

Return to Top

#### Technical Assistance

PPS offers technical assistance at an hourly rate.  Our services are subject to the terms of the contract agreement and are generally non-refundable..

Return to Top
